The outfit I'm going to show you today is
perfect for college students. I chose a denim
jeans model that has a slightly baggy touch.
However, I
chose a white top on top. It didn't match at all,
so I'll make a quick change right away
.  If you leave your shirts off like this, you'll look
so beautiful.
Along with moisturizer and sunscreen, I'm
also applying it to my eyes to elevate them.
Also apply your favorite lipstick shade
.  I am selecting only small studs instead of long earrings
.
Studs match outfits like this perfectly
.  Hope
this should be an idea for many college-going girls.  We
use sticking gums whenever the placement of our dresses changes
.  Then it will be able to
hold the dress perfectly.  These gums
are very affordable.
Hardly ₹150 worth and the final look was here
.  I hope you all
like the outfit.
Let's meet again tomorrow with a new outfit.  Until then, see you
in the next vlog.